# **Audrey Bodine**

Springfield, Missouri (417) 771-1303 audreyEbodine@protonmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/audrey-bodine https://github.com/Audrey-Bodine https://audrey-bodine.github.io/Personal-Site/

### INTRODUCTION

Currently building my website design portfolio with a focus on front-end development. Experienced in entrepreneurial pursuits, I am familiar with creating graphic designs to meet client specifications. During my undergraduate studies, I developed skills in analytical and creative thinking. I am comfortable working and researching independently as well as collaborating in group settings. I excel at communication, particularly in coordinating and managing team objectives.

## **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Science - Information Technology/Application Development**

Missouri State University

August 2021 – May 2023

GPA (Combined Cumulative): 3.85

Springfield, Missouri

The Honor Society of Phi Kappa Phi, Golden Key International Honour Society, Dean's List

#### Associate of Arts - Business

Ozarks Technical Community College

GPA: 4.0

January 2019 – July 2021

Springfield, Missouri

Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society, Chancellor's List

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Social Media Content Manager

Self-employed, @audrey.bo.author

Produces photos for theme consistency

- · Utilizes software for graphic design
- Engages with audience through captions and comments

#### **Graphic Designer**

June 2020 - September 2020

February 2018 - Present

**Bodine Advisors LLC** 

Freelance

Remote

- Adapted concept ideas into digital artwork
- Created infographics to meet client's needs
- · Utilized software to format designs

Website Content Editor October 2019

Innovia Group LLC Freelance

· Researched Raymond James' company website to produce content aligning with mission statement

- · Recommended select written content revisions
- Delivered more edits than client expected, on a quick turnaround time

## **Online Marketplace Seller**

October 2016 - January 2019

Self-employed, Etsy

Freelance

- · Produced greeting cards and digital downloads
- · Interacted with clients to design custom artwork
- · Created product photos for listings

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- Bootstrap
- Graphic design
- · English grammar and punctuation

- Visual Studio Code
- GitHub
- WordPress
- Affinity software
- Procreate

# **RELEVANT COURSES**

- Computer Hardware/Operating Systems
- Art and Experience
- Business Communication
- Technical Writing
- Public Speaking
- Strategic Management and Policy

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Communication
- Organization
- Creativity
- Perseverance
- · Critical thinking
- Collaboration
- Positivity